Guide to the Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 Records, 1836-1975 AIS.1991.08
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Contracts and Arbitration, VI.
  - Employers Proposed Agreement Bewteen Union Employers Printing Section of Pittsburgh and Pittsburgh Typo. No. 7, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh Central Labor Unions Resolutions, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Civic Unity Council Ordinace, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Scale Negotiations, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Agreement, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Proposed Agreement Between Pittsburgh Typo. No. 7 and Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Signed Newspaper Agreement, April 2, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Wage Scales, Hours, and Working Conditions, 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Agreement Between Pittsburgh Typo. Union No. 7 and Pittsburgh Newspaper Publishers' Association, 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Agreement, December 14, 1952-December 13, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Signed Newspaper Agreement, 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - William M. Loughner Appeal, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Pittsburgh Central Labor Unions Resolutions, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Supplemental Agreement and Wages; Signed and Approved, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Proposed Contract, 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Order of Court in the Estate of Thomas J. Flaherty, August 1955 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Brief to the Civil Aeronautics Board, July 7, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Wage Scales, Hours, and Working Condidtions, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Commercial Agreement, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Union Wages and Hours for the Printing Industry, July 1, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Job Scale, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Proposed and Agreed Upon Contract, 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Signed Newspaper Contract, 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Commercial Agreement with Union Employing Printing Section of Pittsburgh; Signed and Approved, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Agreement Signed and Approved by the I.T.U., 1958 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Pittsburgh Central Labor Unions Resolutions, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - National Labor Relations Board Case of the International Typographical Union v. Roger W. Thomas, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Contracts, December 1970 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - List of Prices: Journeyman Printers of Pittsburgh, January 11,1836; 8. (Map-case 3, Drawer 12)
- Officer and Committee Reports, VII.
  This series contains reports and records of officers and committees of the Typographical Union No. 7, as well as reports from sources other than the Typographical Union. President's reports from 1938 to 1951, as well as reports of the Joint Standing Committee from 1939 to 1947, are present. Many other reports written by committees of the Pittsburgh local are included. This series also contains materials from 1940 to 1970 that include pamphlets from annual conferences, programs from anniversary banquets, and reports from conventions with organizations such as the Allied Printing Trades Council, the Union Label Department, and the International Typographical Union.
  - Bryn Mawr Summer School Convention, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Official Report of Charles N. Smith, 1936 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - President's Report, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee and Label Committee Reports, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - President's Report, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Report of Joint Standing Committee, February 1939 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - President's Report, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
  - Dinner Dance Materials, December 1940 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Report of Bills Printed for Legislature, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - President's Report, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - President's Report, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Election Reports, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - President's Report, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Report of the Joint Standing Committee, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - President's Report, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - American Legion Central Pittsburgh Post 707 Reort, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Typographical Conference, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - President's Report, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Report of the Joint Standing Committee, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - President's Report, 1947-1949 (Box 43, Folder 21-23)
  - Hearst Newspaper Chain Conference, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - International Typographical Union 92nd Convention, August 1050 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - President's Report, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Office of Civil Defense Report, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Synopsis Report of the 13th Annual Convention of the Union Label League, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - 50th Anniversary of the Allied Printing Trades Council, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - President's Report, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Report of a Delegate for the 50th Annual Convention of the Pennsylvania Federation of Labor, March 31, 1952-April 4, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Anniversary Proclaimation and Photo, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Report on the Pittsburgh International Contemporary Music Festival, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Convention Call of the Union Label Committee, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Synopsis Report of the 15th Annual Convention of the Union Label Department, November 1953 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Committee on the Sunnyside School Slide, 1953-1954 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Banquet Dance Materials, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Apprentice Committee Materials, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Convention Call of the Union Label Department, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Reports from the Office of the Secretary and Business Manager of Schools Report, July 1954 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report of the School Controller, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report of the County of Alleghany Department of Aviation, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Report of the Committee on Public Health and Welfare, September 1954 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Report of the Committee on Libraries, Parks, and Recreation Facilities, September 1954 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Report of the Committee on Public Safety, September 1954 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Report of the Committee on Independent County Officers and Elections, October 1954 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Population, October 1954 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Report of the Committee on Public Health and Welfare, October 1954 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Report of the Committee on Water Supply and Sanitation, October 1954 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Report of the Committee on Public Health and Welfare, October 1954 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Report of the Pennsylvania Economy League, November 1954 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Report of the Committee on Water Supply and Sanitation, November 1954-December 1954 (Box 43, Folder 52-53)
  - Report of the Committee on Land Use, December 1954 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Report of the Committee on Public Health and Welfare, January 1955 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Report of the Committee on Transportation and Parking, January 1955 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Report of the Committee on Fiscal Practices and Problems, February 1955 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Report of the Committee on Public Schools, April 1955 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Committee on Regional Industrial Development Corp., August 1955 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Report of Committee on Highways and Bridges, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Board of Public Education Report, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Voting Information Report from Typo. Union No. 7, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Board of Public Education Preliminary Budget Report, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Auditorium Budget Report, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Youth Service Committee, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - City of Pittsburgh Budget Report, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Government Leaders Committee on Problems of Urban Mass Transportation, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Youth Service Committee, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 10-11)
  - Photo from a Government Printing Procurement Conference, October 1969 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Materials from the Government Printing Procurement Conference, October 1969 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Award Certificate Presented to President Feigel, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Actuarial Report to the Printing Industry Association of Western Pennsylvania, January 1, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Report on the Typo Union Phase Out Plan Concerning Pensions, January 1, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - 39th Eastern Conference at Philidelphia, March 16-19, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Photograph of the Pittsburgh Point (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Feigel Award, undated (Box 44, Item 1)
  - Conference Photo, undated (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Book of Phone Numbers, undated (Box 44, Volume 1)
  - Drawing of the Pittsburgh Typographical Union No. 7 Building Proposed Addition and Renovations, 1958; 9. (Map-case 3, Drawer 12)
  - Photograph of the First Annual International Allied Printing Trades Association Convention, 1969; 10.
  - Certificate of Affiliation with the Union Label League of Pennsylvania for the Allied Printing Trades Council of Pittsburgh, December 21, 1938; 11.
  - Charter Membership: Allied Printing Trades Council of the American Federation of Labor Pittsburgh District Council Admission to the PA Federation of Labor, March 28, 1939; 12.